The black market is about to get bloody
Pound of Flesh is a action film directed by Ernie Barbarash.
In China to donate his kidney to his dying niece, former black-ops agent Deacon awakes the
day before the operation to find he is the latest victim of organ theft.
Stitched up and pissed-off, Deacon descends from his opulent hotel in search of his stolen
kidney and carves a blood-soaked path through the darkest corners of the city.
The clock is ticking for his niece and with each step he loses blood.
Deacon, played by Jean-Claude Van Damme.
George, played by John Ralston.
Kung, played by Aki Aleong.
Ana, played by Charlotte Peters.
Goran, played by Darren Shahlavi.
Nardo, played by Brahim Achabbakhe.
Pound of Flesh is a 2015 Canadian action film directed by Ernie Barbarash, and
starring Jean-Claude Van Damme, Charlotte Peters, and Darren Shahlavi.
It is the third collaboration between Van Damme and Barbarash (following
Assassination Games in 2011 and Six Bullets in 2012).
The tone is dark.